Guide to the Richard Kostelanetz Collection 1961-1997 MSS.089
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VII: Sound recordings
  - The Gospels Abridged. 1 compact disk., 1990 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Invocations. 1 audiocassettes. (Smithsonian: Folkways)., 1992 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - The John Cage Tribute 2 Compact Disc Set., 1993 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - The Persistence of Hearing 1 audiocassette., undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Little Magazine, 21. CD Rom., undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Oracular Editions. 1, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Tellus: The Audiocassette Magazine., July 1983 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Series VIII: Announcements Of Readings, Exhibitions, etc.
  - Anthology Film Archives, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Arts History: Works, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Arttrax (1994). (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Audio Art (March 18, 1977) (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Book Art (April 9-23, 1978). (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Disintegration -1968 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Echo (March 1969) (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Exposicao de Arte Postal sobre Teatro XI. Mar. 27-Apr. 30, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Extra Biennale de Venise (1978). (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Long Island University Brooklyn Center, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Networking Artists & Poets: Assemblings from the Ruth and Marvin Sackner Archive of Concrete and Visual Poetry. U of Penn. (17 Apr. -27 Jun. 1997). (Box 8, Folder 10a)
  - New Voices - New York (1983). (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - New York Studio School of Drawing, Painting and Sculpture, undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - The 6th Annual New York Book Fair NYU, April 4-6, n. d., undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Stop, Look, and Listen (n. d. ), undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Twenty-Five Years of the Experimental Televison Center (1996). (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Visual Poetry 1970-1995 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art: New American Film and Video Series April 1-29, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Wordsand: An Exhibition of Art with Words, Numbers and Lines in Several Media, undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Works with Words Jun. 7-14, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Writer's Alive: A Confrontation of Literary Celebrity Nov. 291,967. 00, undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Series IX: Miscellaneous
  Computer disks have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
  - Assembling Press Catalogue, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - BOA Editions Limited: New Title. Fall 1993 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - BOA Editions Limited: New Title. Spring 1994 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Item removed to Oversize - located in Mapcase (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Computer Disks: Lingua Blanca #25; Plain Brown Wrapper #21 & #24;#21 and #24; #20; #17 & #18; #31 & #32; #22 & #28; #23 & #29; #25 & #33; #27 and #36; #30 & #34, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Program for Taller de histriones: Teatro De La U. P. R. April 23-24., undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Wordplay. May 22-Jun 1, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Series X: Video recordings
  Video recordings have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
  - A Berlin Lost., 1984 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Berlin Perdu., 1986 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Epiphanies., 1980 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Epiphanies., 1981 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Kaddish., 1991 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Onomatopoeia., 1990 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Openings and Closings., 1975 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Partitions., 1986 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Poetry to See and Poetry to Hear., 1973 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Relationships., 1988 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Stringtwo., 1989 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Ein Verlorenes Berlin., 1983 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Video Strings., 1989 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Video Writing., 1987 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Series XI: Prints
  - Three Visuals, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Black/White, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Kill, Slay.., undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Walk the Earth, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Disintegration, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Me, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Echo, undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Truth, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Numbers One, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - 1024, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Indivisible, undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Increments, undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Two Intervals-I, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Two Intervals-II, undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Parallel Intervals, undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Oversize- Series I: Articles by Kostelanetz
  - Criticizing the Critics. Holiday. 39:03:00158b, d-f., March 1966 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - High Priest of the Electronic Jungle. America Illustrated. 13530-33. In Russian., Undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - How To Be A Difficult Poet. America Illustrated. 248 -1977 39-42. In Russian. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - New Sound for a Plugged-in Age. Look. (Jan. 9, 1968) 45. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - The Two Extremes of Avant-Garde Music. America Illustrated. 13310-13.; In Russian., Undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Oversize- Series II: Periodicals with Poems, Reviews, Introductions, or Short Fiction by Richard Kostelanetz
  - The Albany Review. 3:3 (1989). (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Oversize- Series IX: Miscellaneous
  - Resume -1995 (Map-case 1-E, Folder 7)
- Accretions 1998, 1967-1998
  - Box contains material from series I, II, and VIII., 1967-1996 (Box 11)
  - Box contains material from series I and II., 1992-1998 (Box 12)
  - Box contains material from series II, VI, VII., 1994-1998 (Box 13)
- Accretions 1999, 1998-1999
  - Box contains material from series I., 1994-1999 (Box 13)
  - Box contains material from series II and IX., 1998-1999 (Box 14)
- Accretions 2000, 1968, 1984-2000
  - Box contains material from series I, II, III, VII, VIII, and IX., 1968, 1984-2000 (Box 15)